{"games":[{"levels":[{"queries":[{"question":"What was Canada's first\nnational sport?","availAns":["Soccer","Hockey","Lacrosse","Cricket"],"answer":[false,false,false,true],"type":0},{"question":"What is Canada's official\nsummer sport?","availAns":["Curling","Hockey","Basketball","Lacrosse"],"answer":[false,false,false,true],"type":1},{"question":"What year did Canada's\nmen's soccer team win\ngold at the Olympics?","availAns":["1904","1880","1995","1909"],"answer":[true,false,false,false],"type":2}]},{"queries":[{"question":"Who donated the biggest\nprize in Canadian\nfootball in 1909?","availAns":["Lord Stanley","Earl Grey","Captain Canuck","Arthur Currie"],"answer":[false,true,false,false],"type":0},{"question":"Where did the first\n18-hole golf course\nappear in Canada?","availAns":["Montreal","Niagara Falls","Victoria","Dartmouth"],"answer":[false,false,true,false],"type":1},{"question":"Which Canadian Hockey\nteam was the first to win\ngold at the Olympics? ","availAns":["Winnipeg Falcons","Vancouver Canucks","Montreal Canadians","Calgary Flames"],"answer":[true,false,false,false],"type":2},{"question":"How many common sports\nwere invented by Canadians?","availAns":["2","4","3","5"],"answer":[false,false,true,false],"type":3},{"question":"Who was the first person\nto wear a goalie mask in\na hockey game?","availAns":["Rebbecca Black","Travis Anderson","Elizabeth Graham","Wayne Gretsky"],"answer":[false,false,true,false],"type":4}]},{"queries":[{"question":"What sport did McGill\nUniversity phys-ed\nteacher Dr. James\nNaismith create?","availAns":["Soccer","Lacrosse","Hockey","Basketball"],"answer":[false,false,false,true],"type":0},{"question":"In what year was the\nNational Hockey League\nestablished?","availAns":["1909","1890","1899","1901"],"answer":[true,false,false,false],"type":1},{"question":"Who did the Canadian's\nadopt lacrosse from?","availAns":["USA","Britain","First Nations","French"],"answer":[false,false,true,false],"type":2},{"question":"What city had Canada's\nfirst bowling alley in\n1905?","availAns":["Vancouver","Toronto","Montreal","Regina"],"answer":[false,true,false,false],"type":3},{"question":"Babe Ruth hit his first\nprofessional home run in\nwhich Canadian City?","availAns":["Ottawa","Vancouver","Edmonton","Toronto"],"answer":[false,false,false,true],"type":4},{"question":"In what year did Canada\nfirst compete in the\nParalympics?","availAns":["1949","1968","1955","1931"],"answer":[false,true,false,false],"type":5},{"question":"How many Canadian teams are\nin the NHL?","availAns":["9","5","7","12"],"answer":[false,false,true,false],"type":6}]}],"label":"hockey","right":"applause","wrong":"buzzer","theme":"sports","query":100,"answer":250},{"levels":[{"queries":[{"question":"Name the one famous\nsinger that passed\naway last year?","availAns":["Michael Jackson","Gord Bamford","Gord Downy Jr","Robert Downey Jr"],"answer":[false,false,true,false],"type":0},{"question":"What Canadian rock band\nwas a major component in\nthe video game Guitar\nHero?","availAns":["Rush","Tragically Hip","Nickelback","Loverboy"],"answer":[true,false,false,false],"type":1},{"question":"Name that song: 'Don’t\ncome knockin’ round my\ndoor, don’t wanna see\nyour face no more'?","availAns":["Cherry Pie","That Woman","Go Away","American Woman"],"answer":[false,false,false,true],"type":2}]},{"queries":[{"question":"Mahogany Rush’s guitarist\nFrank Marino is often\ncompared to what other\nfamous guitarist?","availAns":["Jimmy Hendrix","Chad Kroeger","Neil Young","Bryan Adams"],"answer":[true,false,false,false],"type":0},{"question":"Which Vancouver\nbased rock band had hits\nlike 'Pretty Lady',\n'Raise a little Hell'?","availAns":["Hedley","Trooper","Loverboy","Lighthouse"],"answer":[false,true,false,false],"type":1},{"question":"Name the Canadian singer\nthat stared in the Movie\n'Dogma'?","availAns":["Alanis Morrissette","Celine Dion","Drake","Shania Twain"],"answer":[true,false,false,false],"type":2},{"question":"Feist performed her song\n'1 2 3 4' on what PBS show?","availAns":["Cyberchase","Sesame Street","Arthur","Clifford"],"answer":[false,true,false,false],"type":3},{"question":"Who sang the Theme song\nfor the 2002 release of\n'Spiderman'?","availAns":["Adele","Chad Kroeger","Celine Dion","Drake"],"answer":[false,true,false,false],"type":4}]},{"queries":[{"question":"Finish the Line from\nLoverboy’s Working for\nthe Weekend: Everybody’s\nworkin’ for the weekend,\nEverybody wants...","availAns":["a real romance","a true romance","a sweet romance","a new romance"],"answer":[false,false,false,true],"type":0},{"question":"What rock band coined the\nterm 'heavy metal thunder'?","availAns":["Steppenwolf","Loverboy","Tragically Hip","Nickelback"],"answer":[true,false,false,false],"type":1},{"question":"What band won the Juno\nGroup of the Year award in 2017?","availAns":["Pink Floyd","The Beatles","Tragically Hip","Arcade Fire"],"answer":[false,false,true,false],"type":2},{"question":"Who sang 'Summer of '69'?","availAns":["Justin Beiber","Bryan Adams","Chad Kroeger","Neil Young"],"answer":[false,true,false,false],"type":3},{"question":"Hemispheres is recorded\nby what band?","availAns":["Loverboy","Arcade Fire","Hedley","Rush"],"answer":[false,false,false,true],"type":4},{"question":"What Canadian artist has\nbeen inducted into the\nRock Hall of fame both as\na solo artist and as part\nof a band?","availAns":["Neil Young","Chad Kroeger","Andrew Allen","Keith Richards"],"answer":[true,false,false,false],"type":5},{"question":"Name Rush’s first Chart\ntopping single?","availAns":["A part of my Heart","Closer to the Heart","Close my Heart","Open my Heart"],"answer":[false,true,false,false],"type":6},{"question":"Which Canadian band\nfounded the 'Sumersault'\nMusic Festival?","availAns":["Nickelback","Our Lady Peace","Arcade Fire","The Guess Who"],"answer":[false,true,false,false],"type":7}]}],"label":"music","right":"riff","wrong":"feedback","theme":"music","query":100,"answer":300},{"levels":[{"queries":[{"question":"Which province was the\nlast one to join Canada?","availAns":["Manitoba","BC","Newfoundland","Alberta"],"answer":[false,false,true,false],"type":0},{"question":"Confederation was\nofficially proclaimed on\nJuly 1 of what year?","availAns":["1867","1866","1876","1877"],"answer":[true,false,false,false],"type":1},{"question":"Which Province didn't\nattend the Quebec\nConference?","availAns":["Ontario","Labrador","Manitoba","BC"],"answer":[false,false,false,true],"type":2}]},{"queries":[{"question":"When did the name Canada\nbegin first appearing on\nmaps?","availAns":["1550s","1600s","1540s","1580s"],"answer":[true,false,false,false],"type":0},{"question":"In what year did O Canada\nofficially become the\nNational Anthem?","availAns":["1990","1980","1975","1985"],"answer":[false,true,false,false],"type":1},{"question":"In what year did the\nfirst Tim Hortons open in\nHamilton Ontario?","availAns":["1964","1973","1961","1967"],"answer":[true,false,false,false],"type":2},{"question":"Which province was the\nfirst province to grant\nwomen the right to vote?","availAns":["Ontario","Manitoba","Quebec","Saskatchewan"],"answer":[false,true,false,false],"type":3},{"question":"Which superhero was\ncreated by a Canadian?","availAns":["Batman","Superman","Wonder Woman","The Flash"],"answer":[false,true,false,false],"type":4}]},{"queries":[{"question":"What year did Canada\nproduce the toonie?","availAns":["1991","1993","1994","1996"],"answer":[false,false,false,true],"type":0},{"question":"What year did Canada get\nit's official flag?","availAns":["1965","1870","1897","1654"],"answer":[true,false,false,false],"type":1},{"question":"The term 'trick or treat'\nwas first used in which\nCanadian Province?","availAns":["Ontario","Alberta","Quebec","Manitoba"],"answer":[false,true,false,false],"type":2},{"question":"How many time zones are\nthere in Canada?","availAns":["2","3","5","6"],"answer":[false,false,false,true],"type":3},{"question":"What is the name of the\nhighest mountain in\nCanada?","availAns":["Mount Logan","Mount Robson","Mount Steele","Mount Waddington"],"answer":[true,false,false,false],"type":4},{"question":"Thousands of miners\nflocked to which Canadian\nTerritory during the gold\nrush?","availAns":["Nunavut","Yukon","Alaska","Northwest Territories"],"answer":[false,true,false,false],"type":5},{"question":"What famous Canadian led\nthe suffragette movement\nacross the country?","availAns":["Kim Campbell","Celine Dion","Emily Carr","Nellie McClung"],"answer":[false,false,false,true],"type":6}]}],"label":"history","right":"elephant","wrong":"crow","theme":"history","query":100,"answer":250}]}